<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BookDescRoot xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <bookDescList>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000001">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>I've been in enough action to last me a lifetime and a half.

The name's William Cheytac, co-founder and co-Operator of the now defunct Spark's Office, what was once situated in M-Corp. Lemme tell you a story. Sit down, it's a long one. I'll try to skip the boring parts that aren't relevant.

No clue how I got here, ambushed by some moron in a gold jacket swinging around a scythe, almost killing each other. Turns out, that's how you make friends in this city, seeing as that's what happened. He was just some lone merc- er, Fixer, at the time, and I was nobody as far as the world was concerned. So, we became friends, then we became business partners. We were pretty big, in case you somehow didn't know. Ran by a Color, the Golden Spark. Also ran by me, a Grade 1. We also had Rosis, who... I don't even know what the hell he is, honestly. Anyway, despite being an Office of such high prestige, we struggled to make ends meet. Well, he wasn't a Color and I wasn't Grade 1 when we founded the Office, so maybe that's why it took everything we had with the freelance work just to scrape together enough to buy that building. Even after he became a Color, and I became Grade 1, and he took down the Rays of Destruction, we weren't exactly sleeping in king-sized beds with four posts. But we lived. We were even able to recruit more Fixers... but they were more akin to problem causers than problem fixers. They were less than useless, they were goddamn leeches. Taking advantage of Sparky offering room and board out of the goodness of his heart. I had to be the one making sure they stayed off their asses and actually brought in income, but they pocketed more for themselves than they paid us for their rent, I just fucking know it.

Then, something happened... I don't know what it was, he never told me. But out of nowhere we owed the Head four million Ahn. Four fucking million! How does anybody pay that off! That's a death sentence. And death is what came. Spark told the others to pack their shit and scatter. Unfortunately, they listened to him. I, on the other hand, was perfectly content with letting them stay and get slaughtered like the pigs they are by a Claw or two. But I stayed with Spark. I stuck with him.

And then the day came. A Claw came knocking on our door. Even with Spark's ridiculous speed, we had trouble fending that Claw off. Until I... I'm... I'm not sure what I did, but when the dust settled, the Claw was gone. Spark and I within an inch of our lives, but with those broken bones, I swear we lived.





The last words I ever heard were

"You're a problem."

Before the back of my skull was cracked open by an Arbiter.





I miss my old home.

I miss Shauna.

I miss Saville.



Let me out.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000002">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>Rosa...
I bet you feel so much better, now that I'm gone forever. I tell myself that I don't miss you, but that's a lie. It's been decades since I last saw you, Rosa. My foolish, boyish, impulsive love for you has faded, but I would be lying if I said all of it was gone. I've become a better man. But you can't see that now, can you? You'll never get to see it. "Sorry" can't excuse what I said and did. But it's all I can offer you now.

And now, I'm stuck in this accursed Library. Perhaps until the end of time.

Be honest. Lie not to me just to make me feel better; Are you glad that I disappeared?

Tell the others what I did, and what happened to me. Not because I'm proud of those things. They were far from achievements. I have no pride for how I ended up. Tell them so they know not to follow in my footsteps.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000003">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>Blood for our blood god.
Despite hardships, we owe a lot to Nicholas Jaidrane. Our loyalty is the least we can do to repay him for this power and freedom he has granted us. No need to follow the rules, no need to be Fixers for some silly little Office anymore. We're powerful enough to simply take what we want. Food? It's ours. Money? It's ours. Weapons? Come with a snack. Men? Women? We can have our way with whomever strikes our fancy. Blood? It's everywhere! And ours for the taking! Who cares? Certainly not the Head. Certainly not Hana. Certainly not Shi or Liu. Associations have their hands full with roughly a million other problems to stop us. And we can hold ourselves against an Office. The only thing that can stop us is Nicholas. His word is our law. And he has yet to tell us to stop, so...</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000004">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>”Kelsey? It’s me, Alcmene. I know you’ve been struggling. I hate to see you struggle. Nobody to help you, struggling to make ends meet, and you don’t want to give up on [REDACTED]. I get it. You’re desperate, and you want a way out. I wish there was some alternative, but… If desperate times call for desperate measures… I can pull a few strings for you. Moonlight Corporation and Maple Workshop have developed something new, something powerful. If you’re willing… I could make you one of the first beta testers. If it works, it could rocket you up to Color status, and money would mean your problems are over. So… Think about it. Call me back when you have an answer. I still love you, Kells. Alcmene signing out. … Heheh… Just like old times..."



Not gonna lie, I miss my time in Amber Office. Half the reason I took up Alcmene's offer was hoping I could see her again. I didn't... But the visit wasn't awful. Redwood and Ava were super polite and nice and patient and stuff, and the surgery was a success. I'm a Color now, just like Alcmene said... But I don't hold a candle to like, any of the other Colors... Plus, I'm... I can't stargaze anymore. I've started seeing really weird shapes on the moon and in the stars. Shapes that... I really, really, really don't like...

They remind me of how I fucked up. Hard.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000005">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>That damn Golden Spark just had to go and die, didn't he?
We heard word of some edgy black flyin' fuck Distortion called Dark Shepherd, tearin' up M-Corp's Nest. Ain't it M's job to deal wit shit like that in their own Nest? But instead we were commissioned to take care of it. They'd've prolly commissioned Spark's to do it, since they've got a Color 'n all... If the thing didn't explode in some big blue fuckoff fireball a month an' a half back.
Y'see, when a big Corporation like M asks ya to do somethin', there's... They might ask ya, but there really ain't no choice but to do what they ask ya. So it's more like they're tellin' ya. I mean, you really gonna turn down a commission from some big ol' Corporation? I kinda couldn't. They paid me upfront an' ghosted me when I tried to tell 'em my Office can't handle somethin' like that. You heard the DDR on the radio. Homegirl Moses said that bitch was a Star of the City. Bet Spark coulda handled it. But, uhh... We couldn't. Luckily, I had me an invite to the Library as a get outta jail free card in case it turned out we really were fucked against that Dark Shepherd. And whoop dee doo, yes we were. So I signed it, an' had the boys sign it, and off we were.

Turns out it wasn't all that "get outta jail" of a get-outta-jail-free card.

It was like leapin' out of a fryin' pan and right into the fire.

Here's to hopin' somebody back at the Office will pick up on the fact that I ain't comin' back, and they'll take care of Buck for me. Buck, bein' my pet rat. I love the lil' bastard, you know.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000006">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>Top text.
























Bottom text.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000006">
      <BookName />
      <TextList />
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000007">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>I've made an awful lot of rounds around the City...

I used to be a Proxy for the Index. Then the Prescripts told me to leave it behind and join the Liu. Worked as a Liu Fixer, but got let off when Section 2... went up in flames, as it were, in the Library. Heheh... ... It wasn't that funny, actually... And now I'm with NRG Office. I was pretty much hired on the spot when I walked into that interview with Oakley. Because, well, what's harder, working for the Index and the Liu, or stealing a Proxy's sword and fabricating a Liu coat and lying about working for Index and Liu? He didn't seem to care all too much, as he said "experience is experience" and we got right to work.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000008">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>You should be using this to attribute to your key pages.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000009">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>You should be using this to attribute to your key pages.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000010">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>You should be using this to attribute to your key pages.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000011">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>You should be using this to attribute to your key pages.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000012">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>You should be using this to attribute to your key pages.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000013">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>As it turns out... The Golden Spark lives. Why else would Moonlight Corporation's Director Endymion reach out and... "Call in a favor?"

Hmmm~ This will be fun.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000014">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>You should be using this to attribute to your key pages.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000015">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>Hi hi hi! I'm Sunshine! But you could probably tell that already by the cover of the book, or my name on the Key Page, or something! You're reading this in the Credenza though, so... That means you want to know more about me, right? Okay! Well... Uh... My mom's names are Mildred and Parace! They're super cool moms! Although they keep telling me to not use my phenomenal cosmic powers except in self-defense, but that's kinda lame. What's the point of being able to summon flames as hot as the sun if I don't use them as magic fireworks?! ... What were we talking about again?</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000016">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>Hi hi hi! I'm Sunshine! But you could probably tell that already by the cover of the book, or my name on the Key Page, or something! You're reading this in the Credenza though, so... That means you want to know more about me, right? Okay! Well... Uh... My mom's names are Mildred and Parace! They're super cool moms! Although they keep telling me to not use my phenomenal cosmic powers except in self-defense, but that's kinda lame. What's the point of being able to summon flames as hot as the sun if I don't use them as magic fireworks?! ... What were we talking about again?</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000017">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>The LORD is my shepherd; I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie down in green pastures: he leadeth me beside the still waters.
He restoreth my soul: he leadeth me in the paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me; thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table before me in the presence of mine enemies: thou anointest my head with oil; my cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me all the days of my life: and I will dwell in the house of the LORD for ever.

Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me.

Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me.

Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me.

Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me.

Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me.

Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me.

Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000018">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc />
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000019">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>You should be using this to attribute to your key pages.</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
    <BookDesc BookID="10000020">
      <BookName />
      <TextList>
        <Desc>I'm no expert, but I'm pretty sure you should be using this for attaching passives to other key pages, not using this one in battle. I mean, seriously?! ZERO starting light?! No Speed?! ONE HEALTH AND STAGGER RESIST? Come on! You're too smart to use a Reference Sheet in battle!</Desc>
      </TextList>
    </BookDesc>
  </bookDescList>
</BookDescRoot>